同样地，在这里，所有这些项目都在这里，
Again, like here in layers, all this
entire projects in here, and there's
真正能帮助你的事情我们就能快点过去了
something that actually will help you,
let's actually go over that really quick.
因此，存在一个称为 Docker 忽略文件的概念，并且
So, there is a concept of something
called a Docker ignore file, and
Docker 忽略文件很像 gitignore 文件，您说，
a Docker ignore file is much like
a gitignore file, do you say like,
有一堆我不想让你复出的东西
here's a bunch of stuff that I
don't want you to copy over.
实际上是为了证明我的观点
And actually to prove my point here,
再把我的指挥线拉上来如果我说 Docker
let's pull up my command line here again,
and if I say Docker,
就像我的笔记应用程序一样
let's just do Docker run here,
like this my note app, and
如果我说 Ls- lsha别把那不是我想要的
if I say, Ls- lsha,
don't detach that's not what I wanted.
没有复制那个，在默认情况下是这样做的，所以
It didn't copy that over,
it used to do that by default, so
有时它会复制到您的 Git 目录中
sometimes it'll copy for your Git
directory which is not necessarily
你需要的东西这不是 Git 项目
something that you need inside of your,
this isn't a Git project.
但是如果是再一次的话，项目，对，所以我说其实呢，就这样做，
But if it was again, project, right, so
if I said like, in fact, let's just do it,
获取 IT ，并且
get an IT, And
然后我又做了，然后就跑了
then I built it again, and then I ran it
再说，让我们把它带回曝光曝光的那个。
again, Let's get it back to the one
that the expose is on publish.
顺便说一下，我从来没有这样做过，
Just FYI, instead of publish,
I never actually do that,
我是 -p ，就是速记，小写 p，对吧 ?
I do -p which is just the shorthand,
lowercase p, right?
好吧那就好了如果我做了
Okay, so that's working,
now if I do ls- lsha,
发现它正在复制到 git 目录
notice that it's copying
over the git directory,
需要在生产服务器中使用吗 ?
do you need that in
your production server?
否，您是否需要新的生产服务器?
No, do you even want
a new production server?
不，这就像是安全漏洞，对吧 ?
No, it's actually like
a security vulnerability, right?
因为你有你的 git 历史和一堆东西
Because you've your git history and
a bunch of stuff in there, so
其实应该被认为是敏感的信息。
it's actually should be
considered sensitive information.
这样我们就可以明确地将所有我们想要的文件夹命名为这个
So we could go and explicitly name all the
folders that we wanna white list into this
但我觉得这不是很有用的模式
but I don't think that's a very
useful pattern at all, so
我们要做的就是触摸点 dockerignore
what we're gonna do instead is we're
gonna say touch .dockerignore.
如果你写了一个忽略文件的文件，它的格式是一样的，
And if you've ever written a git ignore
file, it's literally the same format,
所以如果我在这里打开它，你可以看到我在这里有一个 dockerignore 文件。
so if I open this here, oops, you can
see I have a dockerignore file here.
如果我放了它那就是我们要忽略的另一个
And if I just put .git, that's one we
wanna ignore and the other one that we've
谈到忽略是 node_modules，我们从不希望复制节点模块。
talked about ignoring is node_modules,
we never wanna copy over node modules.
如果你想把它像个目录但是
And you can put that slash too if you
wanna make it like a directory, but,
它的格式与忽略它的格式相同。
again, it's literally the same
format as a git ignore.
如果它与路径中任何位置的节点模块相匹配，
Just if it matches any node
modules anywhere in the path,
它会说不把它带过来
it'll say nope not bringing that over.
关于医生的问题忽视了吗 ?
Questions about doctor ignore?
每个项目至少应该在其 dockerignore 中具有 .git 。
Every project should at least
have .git in its dockerignore.